seedinfotech.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy

SEED Infotech Limited ("the Company" or "we" or "SEED") is committed to responsible privacy practices and to complying with Information Technology laws and the amended provisions thereto pertaining to electronic records. This electronic record has been generated by a computer system and does not require any authentication.

  1. **Introduction:**  
The Company’s respect for your privacy is paramount. We have policies and procedures to ensure that all personal information i.e. sensitive personal data or information as defined under the Information Technology laws or under the rules framed thereunder is handled in accordance with Indian law. This Privacy Policy sets out our policies on the management of personal information - that is, how we collect personal information, the purposes for which we use this information, and to whom this information is disclosed.  
Please read this privacy policy carefully. By accessing or using our website, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound to all the terms of this privacy policy and our website terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms, exit this page and do not access or use the website. Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the "User" or the "End User") and how we use that information.
  2. **Security of Information:**  
Where ever your personal information is held within SEED, the Company shall take reasonable steps to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information of those who are registered or have online accounts. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.
  3. **Choice of providing personal information:**  
You may choose whether or not to provide personal information to SEED. If you choose not to provide the personal information then you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services that involve our interaction with you.  If you chose to have a relationship with SEED, SEED will continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship. 
  4. **Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites:**  
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you to review the respective website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.
  5. **Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information:**  
We may disclose or share your Personally Identifiable Information with Partners and Affiliates. We also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes. We may also use the information for the purpose of alumni interactions or academic interactions amongst the students.
  6. **Changes to Privacy Policy:**  
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without any notice by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the "Privacy Policy" section of the Website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website. It is the responsibility of each User to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.
  7. **This website uses Google Ad Words:**  
This website uses the Google Ad Words remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. It is to be reiterated that, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.  
You can set preferences for how Google advertises by using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want, you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or permanently using a browser plug-in.
  8. **Questions or suggestions:**  
If you have any questions about the privacy policy of the Company, please e-mail us at [hrd@seedinfotech.com](mailto:hrd@seedinfotech.com) .
